Guide to the Dept. of Government honors theses, 1991-2016
Dept. of Government honors theses, 1991-2016
- Jonathan Furman, "The Search for Liberalism in Kosovo", 2016 (Box 6)
- Nathan Jacobson, "Pork and Polarization: How the Earmark Moratorium Exacerbates Partisan Polarization In the U.S. House of Representatives", 2016 (Box 6)
- Benjamin Leff, "Reality Check - Understanding the Effects of Exposing Partisan Americans to Unanticipated Information About Their Political Leaders", 2016 (Box 6)
- Alexander Lewis, "Police Organizations and Racial Rhetoric: The Link Between Social Unrest and Racialized Political Rhetoric From the Police", 2016 (Box 6)
- Nicholas Raskin, "Rsidential Segregation and Its Impact on Voter Turnout - A Neighborhood-Level Analysis of Political Participation", 2016 (Box 6)
- Margo Stokes, "Explaining Extreme Right Voting in Denmark and Sweden: Looking at Contextual Factors", 2016 (Box 6)
- Caitlan Sussman, "Shifting Into Neutral: Explaining State Neutrality in Immigration Policy in the United States", 2016 (Box 6)
- James Toomey, "Imperium Legum Non Hominum: A Constitutional Theory of Democratic Peace", 2016 (Box 6)
- Gabrielle Velkes, "Online Anonymity: A Political Right or a Haven for Criminality", 2016 (Box 6)
- Samantha Wilhelm, "Is The Roberts Court-ing Business: Class Action in the Wake of Walmart Stores, Inc. v. Dukes", 2016 (Box 6)